翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
We'll kick off the day with some Abrahamic religion.
我们将从亚伯拉罕宗教开始这一天
So we built an IntList last time.
上次构建了一个 IntList
This data structure, it does all the stuff a list can do.
这个数据结构可以做到 List 能做的所有事情
You can add stuff to it.
你可以往 List 中添加东西
You could take that back out.
也可以取出来
It's a sequence of items, from the front and the back, all that stuff.
它是一系列子项，从前到后
Now the specific implementation that we used was,
我们的具体实现是
we had an integer called first
有一个整型 first
and a pointer to the rest of the list called IntList.
和指向 IntList 的 rest 指针
Now this data structure, while you may not have realized it,
现在这个数据结构，你可能没有意识到
was what I call a naked recursive data structure.
就是我所说的裸露的数据结构
Now we'll get a sense of what that means as we move forwards,
我们继续看，一会你就明白了
but basically the idea is, it seem perfectly fine at the time.
基本思想是没问题的
But now this lecture, the fruit of knowledge
但这堂课的知识
is going to reveal to you the grim truth-- that in fact, we were naked all along.
将向你们揭示一个残酷的事实，我们一直是裸露的
So in this lecture, we're going to seek clothing.
在这节课中，我们要寻找衣服
We're going to make the list more like something that's conventional to Java programmers.
让这个 List 更像是 Java 程序员常规使用的
Now there's nothing wrong with IntLists, or nudity, or whatever.
IntList 或者裸体本身没有问题
It's just, it depends on your culture.
这只取决于你的文化
But in the Java culture, having a naked recursive data structure is strange.
在 Java 文化中，裸露的数据结构是很奇怪的
Now in other languages, like the scheme-like languages or in functional languages, you know,
使用类 scheme 或函数式语言
you could do naked recursive data structures all day long.
你可以整天用裸露的数据结构
But in Java, it's just a little awkward.
但 Java 中最好不要
To get a little bit of a flavor for why they're strange,
为什么它们很奇怪
imagine the novice programmer in Java trying to write code that uses IntLists.
想象一下 Java 的新手使用 IntList 编写代码
For them to be able to effectively write code,
为了高效编写代码
they have to be able to know how references work in a pretty deep way.
他们必须深入研究引用的工作方式
The recursion is right there, right on the sleeve of our naked data structure.
递归就在我们裸露的数据结构的袖子上
A sleeve, that's kind of a weird mixed metaphor, but OK, we'll go with it.
袖子，这个比喻很奇怪，就用它吧
But so an IntList, you have to know how pointers work in order to understand what an IntList is.
对于 IntList，你必须知道指针是如何工作的，才能理解 IntList 是什么
The new thing we're going to build, not the case.
我们要造的新东西不是这样的
So how are we going to do that?
要怎么做呢？
What's this new data structure going to look like?
这个新的数据结构会是什么样子呢？
Well, the first step is, we're going to do a rebranding effort.
首先要重新命名
So nudity, that's so 7,000 years ago or however many years ago.
裸体是7000年前或者说很多年前的事了
So we're going to change things.
所以要做一些改变
Instead of having an IntList class, we're going to have an IntNode class.
用 IntNode 类替代 IntList 类
And all that cruft to all those methods that we had in here, we're going to strip them away to become clothes.
我们要脱掉这些方法的缺陷，为它们穿上衣服
I just don't know what is going on with my mixed metaphors.
我不知道怎么想出这个比喻
So I'm going to delete all those methods.
删除所有方法
That's the stripping away.
这就是脱去衣服
And then we're going to rename this to IntNode, IntNode, and IntNode, and IntNode.
然后我们将其重命名为 IntNode
And then I'm going to take these variables
然后操作这些变量
and I'm going to give them new names.
给它们起新名字
Instead of first, I'm going to call this item.
用 item 取代 first
And instead of rest, I'm going to use next.
用 next 取代 rest
And then I'll rename these as well.
这些也改名
You know, it seems nicer.
这样看起来更好
And I'm only doing this painstaking process
做这个艰苦的过程
because I want to make it clear exactly what we're doing.
是因为要弄清我们到底在做什么
So that's the new IntNode class.
这就是新的 IntNode 类
It's like an IntList.
它和 IntList 类似
We just took all the methods away and it compiles.
只是去掉了所有的方法，编译它
So now, we've done this rebranding effort.
我们的重命名工作完成了
We observe that IntNode is now a dumb class.
IntNode 现在是一个哑巴类
It that has no methods.
它没有方法
But we're going to bring back the functionality. Do not worry.
不过别担心，我们会把功能带回来的
Now, of course you might say here,
当然你可以说
this is not any kind of improvement.
这算不上改进
Nothing is better about this.
这没什么好的
And you're right.
你说得对
But we'll get better. Things will improve.
但情况会好转的
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）